

Profile

I have an immense amount of experience working in the technology industry at startups and titans of industry. Some of the tools and technologies that I work with are: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jasmine, jQuery, Python, Flask, SQL/PostgreSQL, Node.JS, Jest, Express.js, Pug.js, React, and React-Redux.

Employment History

Organizer at Pittsburgh Ethereum, Pittsburgh

May 2020 — Present

In charge of organizing speakers, lectures, and coding workshops dedicated to the development of Pittsburgh's local Ethereum community.

Software Engineering Residency at Springboard, Pittsburgh

January 2020 — Present

Built full stack web applications with Python/Flask and JavaScript/React

Designed and developed JSON APIs using Node, Express and SQL

Designed and created optimized pages with HTML, CSS, jQuery

Rendered server side templates with Pug

Authentication and Authorization with bcrypt and JWTs

State management with Redux

Unit testing with Jasmine and integration testing with Jest

Tier 1 Support Agent at DoorDash, Pittsburgh

February 2020 — April 2020

Investigated account-related issues for drivers, merchants, and consumers

Utilized Salesforce for ticketing, emailing, and calling customers to resolve issues promptly

Helped with password resets, chargebacks, account updates, refunds, application updates

Served as a point of contact for all COVID-19 related issues for our delivery platform

Dasher Experience Specialist at DoorDash, Pittsburgh

May 2019 — February 2020

Conducted training sessions for new clients and led on boarding process to ensure Dasher success rate

Details

6147059267

codyrwirth@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn Portfolio GitHub Blog

Skills

Python

JavaScript

SQL

Flask

HTML

CSS

Salesforce

Jira

React.js

Node.js

Redux

Worked directly with cross-functional internal and external teams creating and delivering solutions for our application and internal tools

Building out and analyzing data with G Suite and Chartio offering descriptive analysis (KPI Dashboards; daily, weekly, monthly user activity; orientation activity; no-show rates)

Participated in the Activation Specialists Project to help activate Dashers stuck in the activation funnel offering email support to field questions about the platform

Trained new Dasher Experience Specialists in company policy, procedure, and tools such as Chartio, G Suite, Okta, Slack, Zoom, Jira, etc.

Implementation Consultant at nChannel, Columbus

March 2017 — January 2019

Working with the Solutions Delivery Team, I handled standard, and custom designed data migrations from various eCommerce platforms such as BigCommerce, Volusion, and Magento, to Shopify's platform

Configured and facilitated the development of matrices for configurable/hierarchical data structures

Facilitated one-on-one consultative sessions with clients determining the scope of their migration projects, any additional custom work that may be needed, as well as provide project estimates based upon terms of scope, complexity, and resources

Created custom MySQL queries to pull non-standard data from eCommerce database schemas and provisioned MySQL instances and setup database hosting for a variety of clients using Azure

Diagnosed, researched, and resolved technical issues related to data rendering, data structures, site functionality, data connectivity, API support, hosting, and bugs that arise with a client's specific configuration

Researched and reported software defects and logged them into Jira

Web Developer at Zen.io, Columbus

January 2016 — March 2017

Built personalized landing pages, blogs, and web forms for local businesses utilizing HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript

Designed and built full stack applications with Python/Django such as a job seeking service for community members, and a video subscription service

Designed and built custom email templates for content and marketing teams utilizing HTML/CSS

Product Development Specialist at Facebook, Menlo Park

Worked with Facebook's Product Development Specialist team utilizing Excel to analyze data, utilized pivot tables and statistical techniques to identify trends and patterns emerging in user data, utilizing data visualizations tools such as Tableau

Analyzed and resolved all software bugs or issues in a two day turn around, which improved customer satisfaction

Provided technical expertise to developers experiencing issues, as well as reviewing test cases and user reports of bugs

Gathered and analyzed data in regards to customer insight about current product-related versions and releases on mobile platforms

Collaborated with project management, development, and operations management to determine the products future direction and functionality

Education

B.A., Religious Studies, Denison University, GranvilleAugust 2011 — December 2015

M.S., Information Systems, Keller Graduate School of Management, Pittsburgh

January 2019 — July 2020

1 References

Aiden Craig from DoorDash

aiden.craig@doordash.com · (361) 585-0349

Maceo Owens from DoorDash

maceo.owens@doordash.com · (727) 520-3513

Bethany Rolfson from DoorDash

bethany.rolfson@doordash.com · (315) 489-1057